<!DOCTYPE>
<html>
<head>
<p>
  <strong>meta</strong> &lt;meta charset="utf8" /&gt;
</p>
<title> CheatSheet </title>
</head>

<body>
<h2>
  Word Wide Web General by Chris Bachl
</h2>

<h3>
  What are the most essential technologies that made the World Wide Web such a success?
</h3>

<p>
   The most essential technologies are URL, URI, HTML, HTTP.
</p>

<h3>
  How are resources (html pages, images, etc) addressed in the web?
</h3>

<p>
  With a protocol (http), a hostname (www.example.com), and a file name (index.html).
</p>

<h3>
  What are the general components of a url?
</h3>

<p>
   
      
          A Uniform Resource Locator (URL or web address) has a scheme that includes an information about what it is: a file or a news.
          Considering what it is there will be a specific part, like the username, host, port, path, query, fragment in case the URL starts with Https://

</p>

<h2>
  Web Server
</h2>

<h3>
  What is a web server?
</h3>

<p>
  A Web server is a computer with webserver software
</p>

<h3>
  What does a web server?
</h3>

<p>
  The primary function of a web server is to store, process and deliver web pages to clients.
</p>

<h3>
  How can content be stored on a web server?
</h3>
<p>
  The files that are stored on a webserver are stored in a data base or simply as a file on the desktop.
</p>
<h3>How is content in webpages described</h3>
<p>Web pages delivered are most frequently HTML documents, which may include images,      style sheets and scripts in addition to text content.</p>

<h2>Web Client</h2>

<h3>What is a web client</h3>  
  <p>A web client is every device that is connected to the internet.</p>
 <h3>What does a web client?</h3>
 <p>A web client sends data to servers that will analyze the request and serve the client with the requested information.</p>
 <h3>Web Client and Web Browser is the same?</h3>
 <p>No, as I Sayed the client will only send and receives packages,
          and the web browser will display this content and manage what the client should request next from the server.</p>
<h2>  Hello World</h2>
<h3>What is the html head element?</h3>
<p>the <head> element is a container for metadata (data about data) and is placed between the <html> tag and the <body> tag.</p>
<h3>What does &lt;!DOCTYPE`&gt; html mean?</h3>
<p>
  The <!DOCTYPE> declaration is not an HTML tag; it is an instruction to the web browser about what version of HTML the page is written in.
</p>
<h3>
  What are the two top most elements within the html element?
</h3>
<p>The Body element and the head element</p>
<h3>How to emphasize a text and how is it displayed in the browser?</h3>
<p>
  <em>The &lt;em&gt; tag is a phrase tag. It renders as emphasized text.</em>
</p>
<h3>How to mark up important ext and how is it displayed in the browser?</h3>
<p>
  <strong>The &lt;strong&gt; tag is a phrase tag. It defines important text.</strong>
</p>

</body>

</html>
